searchkut.com 2010-11-20

# 

## Searchkut Privacy Policy

Here at searchkut.com we deliver highly relevant search results to our users while maintaining the most professional service standards. This means we are dedicated to treating you with care and respect.

We encourage anyone using [www.searchkut.com](http://www.searchkut.com/) (our "Site")to make educated decisions about their online practices. To help you do so, this Privacy Policy details important information that will help answer questions regarding personal privacy in relation to the use of our Site. You should also review our [“Terms of Use”](http://searchkut.com/terms.php) before using this Site.

### The Information searchkut.com Collects:

When this Privacy Policy uses the term "personal information," we mean information that might help identify a particular individual, such as the individual's name, postal address, e-mail address, and telephone number.

We do not collect any personal information. We do, however, collect certain other types of data.

_Log File Information:_ Using searchkut.com may result in us receiving non-personal performance and usage information, such as browser type, default language setting, Internet Protocol (IP) address, platform type, the date and time of your request, number of clicks within our environment, an anonymous/random identifier, page views and/or the amount of time spent on our particular pages. We may use this type of information to power the services, identify problems, assess performance and to improve the quality and design of our Site.

_Cookies:_ We do use “cookies.” The cookies we place on your computer are very small text files. They are stored on your hard drive and communicate with our servers only when you are visiting our websites. They allow us to monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors and number of pages viewed. Your web browser is likely already set to accept cookies, yet you may choose to block cookies in your web browser’s settings. Note that blocking cookies may result in some features not being able to function properly.

_Search Revenue:_ We do collect statistical search data. This data does not contain any personally identifying information and is passed through to our search partner for billing purposes.

### Information searchkut.com Discloses

searchkut.com does not collect or disclose personal information with third parties. There is certain non-personal information, as described above, that we may collect and combine with the non-personal information of other individuals (i.e. to aggregate data). Given the nature of this impersonal information, there are no restrictions under this Privacy Policy upon the right of searchkut.com to aggregate your information, and searchkut may use and/or share with third parties the resulting aggregate usage data in any way.

searchkut.com will disclose any information it can access on a user when it believes in good faith that such disclosures are required by law, including, for example, to comply with a court order or subpoena or if we believe, in our sole discretion, that such a disclosure will help to (a) enforce our Terms of Use or any other posted rules or policies; (b) protect your safety or security, including the safety and security of property that belongs to you; and/or (c) protect the safety and security of our Site, searchkut.com, its affiliates and subsidiaries and/or third parties, including the safety and security of property that belongs to searchkut.com or third parties.

This Privacy Policy shall not be construed as preventing us from complying with any court order, court authorized discovery, agency authorized discovery of your information, or ant other legal requirement. 

### Security of Your Personal Information

The security and confidentiality of your information is extremely important to us. We have implemented technical, administrative, and physical security measures to protect user information from unauthorized access and improper use. From time to time, we review our security procedures in order to consider appropriate new technology and methods. Please be aware though that, despite our reasonable efforts, no security measures are impenetrable and any connection or information transmitted to searchkut.com will be at your own risk.

### Links

searchkut.com delivers search results that link to any variety of web properties whose information practices are different than our own. We may also place links to other websites at searchkut.com. searchkut.com only controls information practices at its own site and visitors should consult any other sites' privacy policies when navigating off of the searchkut.com domain, as we have no control over information that is collected or shared by third parties. searchkut.com is, therefore, not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party websites. 

Information you share off of our domain with any website we link to is not collected by searchkut.com and searchkut.com will not be responsible for any such information. 

### Changes and updates to this Privacy Policy

searchkut.com may, at its discretion, add, delete, or modify this Privacy Policy periodically and changes will be reflected by the "Last Updated" reference below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes.

### Contact Information:

If you have any questions or concerns about this searchkut.com Privacy Policy or its implementations please contact us at the following address: 

searchkut.com  

NEED MORE INFO? If there are any terms in this policy you don't understand, visit [www.webopedia.com](http://www.webopedia.com/). 

**Last Updated:** November 11, 2007
